

# **DONG BICH THUC NU**

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER



I always keep up-to-date with the latest technologies and am passionate about learning and applying them to bring value to customers and users.

I am confident in my ability to communicate effectively. Combining creativity and passion, I will continue to learn and contribute to the project in the best.

Over the next 2-3 years, my goal is to attain a Middle Frontend position.

## Work experience

Feb 2023 - May 2023

Internal Project

Frontend Developer at NFQ

It is an internal project and it has been designed from the ground up to make career progression and personal growth fun and engaging through gamification and tangible rewards. It is built to enhance or even replace the usual cycle of performance reviews.

#### Technologies used

Vuejs, Typescript, Naive UI, TailwindCSS

Jan 2022 - May 2023

**DoctorCare** 

**Personal Project** 

A website that supports users to schedule medical appointments online without the need to physically go to the clinic and wait for a queue number.

#### Technologies used

Reactis, Nodeis, Postgresgl, Bootstrap 4



Phone

0845848284



**Email** 



thucnu0608@gmail.com



**Address** 

Can Tho, Vietnam



Dob

06/08/2001



Gender



Female



https://github.com/thucnu



### **Education**

Can Tho University | 2019 - Present

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

GPA: 3.3/4.0

Certificate of Excellent Student for academic years 2020-2021 and 2021-2022.

Scholarship for good students in the second semester of academic year 2019-2020, excellent students of academic year 2020-2021, and academic year 2021-2022.

Academic exchange at the Research and Development Faculty, Royal University of Phnom Penh (RUPP), Cambodia in 2022.



#### **Skills**

ReactJS

Github

JavaScript

Communication

TypeScript

Teamwork

Naive UI

English

**TailwindCSS** 

Bootstrap 4